atheists.org 2009-06-16

# American Atheists | Orphans: Privacy Statement

## Privacy Statement

This is the web site of the American Atheists. 

Our postal address is: 

PO BOX 5733  
Parsippany, NJ 07054-6733

Our phone is:   
908-276-7300

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

The information we collect is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences including login status.  

If you supply us with your postal address or other information on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.

With respect to Ad Servers: We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will contact you before we use your data for these new purposes to notify you of the policy change and to provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information [including proprietary information] that we maintain about them, transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them, communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to our site (e.g., e-mails, customer inquiries), contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them .

Consumers can access this information by contacting us at the above number, postal address, or via our contact form.  

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.

style="position:relative;width:660px;height:600px;">

## Privacy Statement

This is the web site of the American Atheists. 

Our postal address is: 

PO BOX 5733  
Parsippany, NJ 07054-6733

Our phone is:   
908-276-7300

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

The information we collect is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences including login status.  

If you supply us with your postal address or other information on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.

With respect to Ad Servers: We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will contact you before we use your data for these new purposes to notify you of the policy change and to provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information [including proprietary information] that we maintain about them, transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them, communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to our site (e.g., e-mails, customer inquiries), contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them .

Consumers can access this information by contacting us at the above number, postal address, or via our contact form.  

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.

### Choose an Image for the Page

recommended dimensions: 800 x 200   required type: jpg  
( click here to clear out page image)

return to page
